This video introduces the water-washing effect preset function of the bullfrog.
It can achieve the expression of a real bullfrog.
From the 2025.1 version, the material material type has been added to the Diningbo type.
Using this function, you can adjust the water-washing process preset and various parameters to show various water-washing effects.
This function is based on the bullfrog texture and basic texture diagram for water-washing.
We will use this bullfrog to show the function.
First, select the bullfrog fabric in the object window.
Then, in the property editor below, change the material type to Diningbo.
When the material type is set to Diningbo, you can see that the water-washing process type option will appear below.
Use the water-washing type to select the bullfrog cloth.
Select the water-washing process to preview the effect.
According to the selected water-washing type, the detailed properties or parameters below will change accordingly.
.
You can freely adjust the parameters.
Next, we will quickly understand the different water-washing types that can be displayed through this picture.
First, its default setting is for the water-washing type.
It refers to the original bullfrog cloth that has not been water-washed.
Only the texture diagram of the original fabric is applied.
The Diningbo type is the most basic water-washing process.
It can evenly color and soften the fabric.
At the same time, it retains the original color of the bullfrog to the maximum extent.
The speed-washing type can be applied through the light pattern.
It can slightly fade the color and soften the fabric.
The nature-painting effect is as if it has been worn many times.
At the same time, it avoids obvious discoloration.
The Dining-washing technique is used to add floating friction to the fabric during the washing process.
It has a nature-painting effect.
And it forms a clear contrast pattern.
The Dining-washing type is used for special chemical processing.
It forms a strong contrast between the Dining-washing type and the Dining-washing type.
The visual effect is clear.
The Dining-washing technique makes the color of the bullfrog lighter.
The strength of the processing can be expressed from a subtle tone.
It changes to an almost white multi-layer effect.
The Dining-washing technique can achieve the natural anti-painting effect of even discoloration.
It makes the bullfrog appear in a subtle and unified light tone.
Finally, the customized Dining-washing type supports the application of customized Dining-washing patterns.
It can infinitely expand the individualization of Dining-washing effects.
It achieves a unique design expression.
Now let's go back to the Dining-washing interface.
We will apply the two Dining-washing types, Dining-washing and Dining-washing, to this bullfrog.
And see how to adjust their parameters to show different bullfrog Dining-washing effects.
First, in the property editor.
Change the Dining-washing process type to Dining-washing.
You can see the Dining-washing effect of the entire pants in the 3D window.
And click on the little triangle.
The Dining-washing pattern corresponding to the Dining-washing type will appear at the bottom.
The basic pattern of the pattern and the fabric are naturally integrated.
Thus, the bullfrog Dining-washing effect of Dining-washing is shown.
If you do not use Dining-washing, you can also add the Dining-washing pattern you want.
Then the Dining-washing process type will be automatically changed to user customized.
Thus, you can achieve the customized Dining-washing effect you want.
Next, we will see the detailed properties of the selected Dining-washing type.
The first thing we see is the discoloration intensity.
As the name implies, it is an option to control the overall intensity of the discoloration effect.
If you move the slider to the right to increase the value.
The contrast of the dark area of ​​the pants will be more obvious.
The maximum limit creates the feeling of wearing for a long time.
See the mixing mode below.
Click on the download menu to switch between various mixing options.
For example, normal, flat bottom and green.
These options determine how the Dining-washing effect is mixed with the fabric pattern of the bullfrog.
Specifically, the Dining-washing function can naturally increase the contrast.
Make the dark part of the Dining-washing pattern dark.
And the bright part becomes brighter in the original Dining-washing pattern.
Due to the most realistic simulation of the Dining-washing function.
The discoloration and discoloration effects in the actual Dining-washing process.
Therefore, it is recommended that in most of the Dining-washing settings.
Use the Dining-washing function to get the most natural and realistic effect.
The absorption of the bottom.
The number determines the depth and width of the Dining-washing effect absorbed by the fabric.
Increasing this value can increase the range of Dining-washing effects.
To bring a more natural and harmonious feeling.
The duration of the week is the function of adjusting the Dining-washing time.
Increasing this value can extend the Dining-washing time.
To remove more dye on the jeans.
So you can see the overall color of the pants.
Increase thelle value for small 처음.
We are that the last Dining-washing effect.
But to apply this option.
We have to pre-apply Lucy fold in the corresponding area.
Now this case increases the Dining-washing value.
You can also see that it's applied to the side of the pants.
You can see that the texture of the sewing wrinkle is darker and the outline is clearer.
On the contrary, the lower the number, the more blurred the wrinkle.
By pre-applying the sewing wrinkle and adjusting the number of creases,
you can show a more realistic cowhide creasing water wash effect.
Next, change the water-washing technique to rinsing.
After changing the water-washing type, you will see that the overall color of the pants becomes brighter,
as if it has been rinsed with a chemical.
And you can see that the following detailed options are different from the 10 model types we just chose.
First is the rinsing concentration. It is set to the strength of the water-washing effect.
As the number grows, the water-washing effect can be enhanced to maximize the rinsing effect,
and the color of more cowhide cloth can be removed to make it brighter.
On the contrary, this value can be reduced to show a slight rinsing effect.
For rinsing, we can change the mixing mode.
The rinsing mode is called soft light.
The contrast of soft light is not as good as the strong one.
Therefore, the rinsing part is smoothly integrated with the original cowhide fabric.
Therefore, according to the different mixing options that need to be set,
even if you use the same water-washing type, you can achieve more water-washing effects.
Finally, you can adjust other parameters, such as absorbency or creasing wear to enhance the detail performance.
Especially on the pants of the rinsing pot,
the water-washing effect can be added to the creasing area.
It can show a more three-dimensional discoloration effect,
creating a real wear and tear mark and not a simple color discoloration,
and thus presenting a more layered workmanship effect.
To choose a different water-washing type, the first adjustment parameters at the bottom will also be different,
but the adjustment thinking is the same.
Using the water-washing preset, you can choose the water-washing type you need in the attribute editor,
and adjust the detailed attribute.
It will quickly present your cowhide fabric in a more realistic way.